RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
- Part I Subject Files, 1972-1977
  - Letters from Gov. Grasso (Box 397)
    - Baba-Bapt (O) (Box 398)
    - Bark-Bazz (O) (Box 398)
    - Beach-Benz (O) (Box 399)
    - Beril-Berr (O) (Box 399)
    - Bh-Bly (O) (Box 399)
    - Boa-Boz (O) (Box 400)
    - Brac-Brit (O) (Box 400)
    - Broad-Bruz (O) (Box 400)
    - Bry-Buz (O) (Box 401)
    - Caba-Cao (O) (Box 401)
    - Cap-Carpp (Box 401)
    - Carr-Caz (O) (Box 402)
    - Cear-Chot (O) (Box 402)
    - Chi-Cly (O) (Box 402)
    - Coa-Cok (O) (Box 403)
    - Col-Coz (O) (Box 403)
    - Cr-Cz (O) (Box 404)
    - Da-Del (O) (Box 404)
    - Del-Don (O) (Box 405)
    - Donahue, Leo (O) (Box 405)
    - Don-Dorn (O) (Box 405)
    - Doro-Epst (O) (Box 406)
    - Epst-Feyr (O) (Box 407)
    - Fi-Fl (O) (Box 407)
    - Foc-Fys (O) (Box 408)
    - Gab-Gew (O) (Box 408)
    - Gfe-Gok (O) (Box 409)
    - Gola-Gozz (O) (Box 409)
    - Gra-Gs (O) (Box 410)
    - Guag-Gz (O) (Box 410)
    - Haac-Hann (O) (Box 410)
    - Hand-Hirs (O) (Box 411)
    - Hirt-Hott (O) (Box 412)
    - Hou-Hy (O) (Box 412)
    - Iaco-Jaro (O) (Box 412)
    - Jaro-Jone (O) (Box 413)
    - Jones-Jus (O) (Box 413)
    - Kaat-Kazm (O) (Box 413)
    - Ke (O) (Box 414)
    - Kh-Kn (O) (Box 414)
    - Koba-Kowa (O) (Box 414)
    - Kowa-Kyle (O) (Box 415)
    - Lab-Lar (O) (Box 415)
    - Las-Led (O) (Box 415)
    - Lee-Lezo (O) (Box 416)
    - Lhe-Lon (O) (Box 416)
    - Look-Luby (O) (Box 416)
    - Luby-Mars (O) (Box 417)
    - Mars-McKe (O) (Box 418)
    - McKe-Mess (O) (Box 419)
    - Mia-Mis (O) (Box 419)
    - Mit-Mom (O) (Box 420)
    - Mon-Mori (O) (Box 420)
    - Morl-Nard (O) (Box 420)
    - Nard-Nh (O) (Box 421)
    - Nia-Nys (O) (Box 421)
    - Oma-Oz (O) (Box 421)
    - Pabi-Papa (O) (Box 421)
    - Papa-Pete (O) (Box 422)
    - Pete-Pezz (O) (Box 423)
    - Pfa-Pla (O) (Box 423)
    - Poad-Pros (O) (Box 423)
    - Prut-Q (O) (Box 423)
    - Raab-Robe (O) (Box 424)
    - Robe-Roja (O) (Box 425)
    - Rok-Rox (O) (Box 425)
    - Roy-Rz (O) (Box 425)
    - Saa-St.V (O) (Box 425)
    - Salk-Salu (O) (Box 425)
    - Salu-Schl (O) (Box 426)
    - Sa-Sm (O) (Box 426)
    - Sap-Schaff (O) (Box 426)
    - Schm-Scz (O) (Box 426)
    - Seab-Simt (O) (Box 427)
    - Smith (O) (Box 428)
    - Snav-Spur (O) (Box 428)
    - Sq-Stav (O) (Box 428)
    - Syc-Swif (O) (Box 428)
    - Swif-Sull (O) (Box 429)
    - T-Taz (O) (Box 429)
    - Te-Tez (O) (Box 429)
    - Th-Thz (O) (Box 430)
    - Ti-Toz (O) (Box 430)
    - Tra-Tur (O) (Box 430)
- Part II Subject Files, 1971-1980
  - Abortion Letter #31 (B), 1978 March (Box 431)
  - [Acknowledgments] (Box 431)
    - [A-L] (O), 1978-1979 (Box 431)
    - [M-Z] (O), 1978-1979 (Box 431)
  - [Administrative Services] (O), 1978-1979 (Box 431)
  - [Affirmative Action], 1978-1979 (Box 431)
  - [Affirmative Action - Annual Reports], 1974-1975 (Box 431)
  - [Affirmative Action - Status Reports], 1978 (Box 431)
  - [Aging - Blue Ribbon Committee], 1978 (Box 431)
  - [Aging] (Box 432)
    - [Home Care Budget] (I), 1979 (Box 432)
    - Letters to and from Charles Odell, 1975-1977 (Box 432)
    - [Project Triage] (B), 1977-1979 (Box 432)
    - [Sail Program] (I) (Box 432)
    - State Plan on Aging, 1979 (Box 432)
    - Waiving Parking Fees at State Parks (B), 1977-1979 (Box 432)
    - Wyandover Nursing Home (B), 1977 (Box 432)
  - [Agriculture] - memos to and from Commissioner Wilbur, 1975-1976 (Box 432)
  - [Alcohol/Alcoholism] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 432)
  - [Anthropology - Margaret Mead Fund], 1980 (Box 432)
  - [Annual Reports] (B), 1975-1977 (Box 433)
  - [Annual Reports] (B), 1978 (Box 433)
  - [Annual Reports] (B), 1979 (Box 433)
  - [Appointments] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 433)
  - [Architects, Archeology] (B), 1978 (Box 433)
  - Armory - Bristol (B), 1978 (Box 433)
  - Armory - New Britain (B), 1975-1978 (Box 433)
  - [Arts - Conn. Commission On]: [Letters A-G] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 434)
  - [Arts - Grants] [H-Z] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 434)
  - [Arts - National Endowment for], 1978 (Box 434)
  - [Banking] (Box 434)
    - [A-G] (B), 1978 (Box 434)
    - [H-W] (Box 434)
  - [Banking - Glastonbury Bank & Trust], 1979 (Box 434)
  - [Banking - Misc..], 1978-1979 (Box 434)
  - Blizzard ‘78 - General (B), 1978 (Box 434)
  - Blizzard ‘78 - #30 (B), 1978 February (Box 435)
  - [Blizzard ‘78] Taxes for Help During Storm Larry - U.S. Department of Transportation (O) (Box 435)
  - [Bond Commission] (B), 1978 (Box 435)
  - Bond Commission/Minutes of Meeting, 1979 June 22 (Box 435)
  - [British Railways Board], 1979 (Box 435)
  - Budget Request #10 (B), 1978 (Box 435)
  - [Building Inspector] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 435)
  - [Canada], 1980 (Box 435)
  - [Carnegie Corp. of N.Y.], 1979 (Box 435)
  - Caucus of Conn. Democrats, 1978 (Box 435)
  - Challenges Our State Faces Today (B), 1978 (Box 435)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1978-1979 (Box 435)
  - [Child Abuse] (B), 1978 (Box 435)
  - [Children and Youth Services (DCYS)] (B), 1979 (Box 436)
  - [Children and Youth Services] (Box 436)
    - [Group Homes] (B), 1978 (Box 436)
    - [A-C] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 436)
    - [D-G] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 436)
    - [H-Q] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 436)
    - [R-Z] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 436)
    - Memos to and from Maloney, 1975-1979 (Box 436)
  - Civic Center Roof Collapse (B), 1978 (Box 436)
  - [Civil Aeronautics Board], 1979 (Box 437)
  - Civil Preparedness Conference for Hispanics - Tx’s for Attending (O), 1978, 1979 July (Box 437)
  - [Civil Preparedness - Letters A-Z] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 437)
  - [Civil Preparedness - Misc..] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 437)
  - [Civil Preparedness - Waterford Drill], 1978 (Box 437)
  - [Civil Rights Commission - U.S.], 1978 (Box 437)
  - [Civil Science Commission - U.S.], 1978 (Box 437)
  - [Claims Commission] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 437)
  - Clippings A-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 437)
  - [Coalition of New England Governors (CONEG)] (O), 1978-1979 (Box 437)
  - Commendation/Highway Departments for Work During Winter Storms (O), 1978 (Box 437)
  - Commendation/People who Worked During Winter Storms (O), 1978 (Box 437)
  - Commendations #12 (B), 1978-1979 (Box 437)
  - [Commerce - Hartford Camber of], 1979 (Box 437)
  - [Commerce - Letters:] (Box 438)
    - A-D (B), 1978 -1979 (Box 438)
    - E-H (B), 1978-1979 (Box 438)
    - J-O (B), 1978-1979 (Box 438)
    - P-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 438)
  - [Commerce - Misc.], 1978 (Box 439)
  - [Commerce - Small Business Admin.], 1978 (Box 439)
  - [Commerce - Stanford Weather Station] (B), 1978 (Box 439)
  - [Commerce - U.S. Dept. of], 1980 (Box 439)
  - [Communication - Emergency System], 1979 (Box 439)
  - [Community Affairs - DCA] (Box 439)
    - [Day Care] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 439)
    - [Day Care - Labor] (Box 439)
    - [A-I] (B), 1979 (Box 439)
    - [J-Z] (B), 1978 (Box 439)
    - [Memos to and from Rice], 1978 (Box 439)
    - [Misc.] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 439)
  - [Community Affairs (DCA) - West End Civic Assoc.], 1978 (Box 440)
  - [Community Services] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 440)
  - Community Service Programs (B), 1978 (Box 440)
  - [Comptroller - Letters A-Z] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 440)
  - [Comptroller - Memos to and from Caldwell], 1978-1979 (Box 440)
  - [Concerned Citizens Letters A-K] (B), 1978 (Box 440)
  - [Concerned Citizens Letters L-Z] (B), 1978 (Box 440)
  - [Conference of Municipalities - Conn..], 1979 (Box 440)
  - [Congressional Awards Program], 1979 (Box 440)
  - Congressional/Clearinghouse on Women’s Rights, 1978 (Box 441)
  - [Congressional Delegation] (O), 1975-1978 (Box 441)
  - Conn. Product development Corp. (to Commercial Banks) (O), 1979 April 18 (Box 441)
  - [Constitution - Amendments], 1971-1973 (Box 441)
  - [Construction - Misc.], 1978 (Box 441)
  - [Consumer Advisory Council], 1978 (Box 441)
  - [Consumer Counsel] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 441)
  - Consumer Protection - Home Insulation (General), 1977-1978 (Box 441)
  - Consumer Protection - Home Insulation Task Force, 1987 (Box 441)
  - [Consumer Protection - Letters] (Box 441)
    - A-G (B), 1978-1979 (Box 441)
    - H-M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 441)
    - N-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 441)
  - [Consumer protection - memos to and from Commissioner Heslin], 1978-1979 (Box 442)
  - [Convention bureau] (B), 1978 (Box 442)
  - Corrections/Public/Private Expansion Program (B), 1979 March 27 (Box 442)
  - [Develop Authority of Conn. - Minutes], 1979; 2 folders (Box 442)
  - [Development - Project Turtle], 1978-1979 (Box 442)
  - [Discrimination Against Women State Employees] (I), 1979 (Box 442)
  - [Discrimination Against Women State Employees] (I), 1979 (Box 443)
  - [Drugs - Council on Alcohol &Drug Abuse] (B), 1978 (Box 443)
  - Drugs - Discrimination of Marijuana (B), 1978-1979 (Box 443)
  - [Eastern States Exposition], 1978 (Box 443)
  - [East Hartford], 1979 (Box 443)
  - [Economic Development Authority] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 443)
  - [Economic Development - Hartford Corp.], 1979 (Box 443)
  - [Economic Development - Housing] (B), 1979 (Box 443)
  - [Economic Development - Title IX, Waterbury], 1979 (Box 443)
  - [Economy - Misc.] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 443)
  - Editorials, 1978-1979 (Box 443)
  - [Education] (Box 444)
    - [Adult], 1979 (Box 444)
    - Allocation of State Aid to Education (B), 1979 February 14 (Box 444)
    - [Alternative Education for Prevention of Delinquency], 1980 (Box 444)
    - [Board of Higher Education], 1979-1980 (Box 444)
    - [Board of Trustees], 1978-1979 (Box 444)
    - Bridgeport teachers Strike (Box 444)
    - Budget Cut Petitions (Box 444)
    - [Carnage Council On Higher Education], 1980 (Box 445)
    - [Central Connecticut State College] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 445)
    - [Commission of the States], 1978-1979 (Box 445)
    - [Commission on Higher Education] (Box 445)
      - Letters A-I (B), 1978-1979 (Box 445)
      - Letters J-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 445)
    - [Community Colleges] (Box 446)
      - Budget (B), 1978 (Box 446)
      - [Budget Letters] (I), 1979; 3 folders (Box 446)
      - Budget Proposal #23 (O), 1979 February 2 (Box 446)
      - [Budget] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 446)
    - [Community Colleges] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 447)
    - Community Colleges Professional Staff Negotiations (B), 1979 August (Box 447)
    - Manchester Community College - Permanent campus (B), 1978 (Box 447)
    - Tunxis Community College Purchase (B), 1979 October (Box 447)
    - [Connecticut State Board - Minutes], 1980 May 7, 1980 September 3 (Box 447)
    - [Connecticut Student Loan Foundation], 1975 (Box 447)
    - [Founding] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 447)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1980 (Box 447)
    - [Memos to and from Mr. Toftulon], 1978 (Box 447)
    - [Miscellaneous Correspondence] (Box 448)
      - A-L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 448)
      - M-R (B), 1978-1979 (Box 448)
      - S-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 448)
    - [Petition COPUS/CSICP] (I), 1978-1979 (Box 448)
    - [Racial Imbalance] (B), 1978 (Box 448)
    - [Reading is Fundamental - RIF] (I), 1978 (Box 448)
    - [Special Education - Including the Blind] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 449)
    - [State College Budget letters] (I), 1979; 3 folders (Box 449)
    - [State Dept. of, Bulletin], 1979 (Box 449)
    - [Teacher’s Retirement] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 449)
    - [University of Bridgeport] (Box 449)
    - [UCONN Board of Trustees]: Finance Committee, 1979 (Box 449)
    - [UCONN Board of Trustees] (Box 450)
      - [Finance Committee], [1980]; 3 folders (Box 450)
      - [Health/Hospital Meetings], 1978-1979 (Box 450)
      - [Meeting Agenda], 1979 January 12-February 9 (Box 450)
      - [Meeting Agenda], 1979 March 16-July 13 (Box 451)
      - [Meeting Agenda], 1979 July 13-1980 January 11 (Box 452)
      - [Meeting Agenda], 1980 February 8-1980 June 13 (Box 453)
    - Meeting Minutes, Misc., 1979-1980; 3 folders (Box 454)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 455)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 455)
    - [UCONN] (Box 455)
      - [Branches/Schools], 1978-1979 (Box 455)
      - [Budget] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 455)
      - [Centennial], 1979-1980 (Box 455)
      - [Health Center Letters] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 455)
      - [Health Center Misc.] (Box 455)
      - [Master of Business Administration, Letters] (B), 1979 (Box 455)
      - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 455)
      - [Miscellaneous Correspondence] (Box 456)
        - A-F (B), 1978-1979 (Box 456)
        - G-M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 456)
        - N-Z (B) (Box 456)
      - [Veterinary School] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 456)
      - [Vocational/Rehabilitation] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 456)
      - [Western Conn. State College] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 456)
      - [Yale/Trinity], 1978-1979 (Box 456)
  - Elections (B), 1977-1979 (Box 457)
  - Electric Boat Layoffs #33 (B), 1978 January (Box 457)
  - Electrical Examiners (B), 1978 (Box 457)
  - [Embalmers/Funerals] (B), 1978 (Box 457)
  - [Employment], 1978-1979 (Box 457)
  - [Employment - Recommendations] (B), 1977-1979 (Box 457)
  - [Energy] (Box 457)
    - Conservation Awareness Program by Pequabuck Valley District Boy Scouts (O) (Box 457)
    - Crisis Intervention (B), 1978 (Box 457)
    - Emergency Assistance Letter to Gas &Electric Companies (O), 1978 November 16 (Box 457)
    - Gasoline Shortage - Letters (I), 1979; 3 folders (Box 457)
    - Gasoline Shortage - letters (I), 1979; 2 folders (Box 458)
    - Governor’s Southwestern Meeting, 1979 June 27 (Box 458)
    - Mayors &First Selectman/Energy Situation (O), 1979 June 1 (Box 458)
    - [Nuclear Power] (Box 458)
      - [Letters] (B), [1978] (Box 458)
      - [Letters] (B), [1979] (Box 458)
      - [Letters] (B), [1979] (Box 459)
      - Millstone Power Plant #38 - 2778 (B) (Box 459)
      - Millstone/Tx’s to Nuclear Regulatory Comm., 1978 (Box 459)
      - Petition to Investigate Millstone I (I), 1978 June 15 (Box 459)
      - Power Plants #64 (B), 1978 (Box 459)
      - Seabrook (B), 1978 (Box 459)
      - Seabrook Nuclear Power site Petition &Letters (B), 1978 June 14 (Box 459)
    - Office of Policy &Management (COPM) (Box 459)
      - Energy Congress (B), 1978 (Box 459)
      - Energy Exemptions (Requests for) (B), 1979 (Box 459)
      - Energy/Gasoline Pricing (O) (Box 459)
      - Repetitions, 1979 May 15 (Box 459)
      - Energy/Gasoline Shortage to all Major Oil Companies (O), 1979 July 3 (Box 459)
    - Office of Policy &Management (DPM) (Box 460)
      - [Letters A-D] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 460)
      - [Letters E-G] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 460)
      - [Letters H-M] (1978-79) (B), 1978-1979 (Box 460)
      - [Letters N-R] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 460)
      - [Letters S-Z] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 460)
    - Letters Mis-directed to Motor Vehicles (B), 1979 (Box 460)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1978-1980 (Box 460)
    - Office of Policy &Management 7 (OPM) (Box 461)
      - Odd-Even Mag. (B), 1979 September (Box 461)
      - Odd-Even Rationing (B), 1979 (Box 461)
      - [Solar] (B), 1978 (Box 461)
      - Weekend Closing (B), 1979 (Box 461)
    - Shutoffs for this Winter (B), 1978 December 1 (Box 461)
    - Solar Energy Alliance (B), 1978 (Box 461)
  - Engineers (B), 1978 (Box 461)
  - [Environment] (Box 461)
    - A (B), 1978-1979 (Box 461)
    - B (B), 1978-1979 (Box 461)
    - C (B), 1978-1979 (Box 461)
    - D (B), 1978-1979 (Box 462)
    - E, F (B), 1978-1979 (Box 462)
    - G (B), 1978-1979 (Box 462)
    - H, I, J (B), 1978-1979 (Box 462)
    - K, L, 1978-1979 (Box 462)
    - M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 463)
    - N,O,P (B), 1978-1979 (Box 463)
    - R (B), 1978-1979 (Box 463)
    - S (B), 1978-1979 (Box 463)
    - T,U,V (B), 1978-1979 (Box 463)
    - W,X,Y,Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 463)
  - [Environment] (Box 464)
    - [Air Quality], 1979 (Box 464)
    - [Air Quality Letters] (B), 1979 (Box 464)
    - [Air Quality/Pollution/Compliance] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 464)
    - [Clean Air Act] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 464)
    - [Coastal Area Management] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 464)
    - [Communications From Sec. of Army, (water resources)], 1979 (Box 464)
    - [Conn. Resource Recovery Authority CRRA] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 464)
    - [Conn. River] (B), 1976-1978 (Box 464)
    - [Conservation/Preservation] (B), 1978 (Box 464)
    - [Council on Environmental Quality CEQ] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 464)
    - [Flooding/Fisheries] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 465)
    - [Housatonic River], 1978 (Box 465)
    - [Lakes/Rivers] (B), 1978 (Box 465)
    - [Landfills] (B), 1977-1979 (Box 465)
    - [Long Island Sound - Bridge/Ferry] (B), 1977-1979 (Box 465)
    - [Military/Dams] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 465)
    - [Misc. Correspondence] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 465)
    - [Oil/Outer Continental Shelf], 1978 (Box 465)
    - [New England River Basin Commission - NERBC], 1978 (Box 466)
    - [PCB’s], 1980 (Box 466)
    - [Solid Waste] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 466)
    - State Owned Land for a Landfill Operation (B), 1978 (Box 466)
    - [State parks/Outdoors] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 466)
    - [Washington State], 1980 (Box 466)
    - Western Ct. Water Supply (Housatonic River) (B), 1978 (Box 466)
    - [Water Quality/Wetlands], 1978 (Box 466)
    - [Wildlife/Plants/Endangered Species] (B), 1978 (Box 466)
  - [ERA]: A-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 466)
  - ERA - Encouragement &Support #8 (B), 1978 July (Box 466)
  - ERA - Opposed - #8A (B), 1978 (Box 467)
  - ERA - State Funds for Travel through Unratified States (B), 1978-1979 (Box 467)
  - Ethnics Comm., 1978-1979 (Box 467)
  - [Executive Orders], 1975-1979 (Box 467)
  - Extradition/Mag. (B), 1979 January (Box 467)
  - [Family Relations] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 467)
  - [Farmer’s Home Administration], 1979 (Box 467)
  - [Federal Communications Commission], 1978-1980 (Box 467)
  - [Federal Matter] - A-L (B), 1977-1978 (Box 467)
  - [Federal Matter] - M-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 467)
  - [Federal Trade Commission - ETC] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 468)
  - Filer Commission (B), 1978 (Box 468)
  - Finance Advisory Committee - Minutes Meeting (Box 468)
  - Flags/Granted (B), 1978 - 1979 (Box 468)
  - Fire Marshal/Enfield Faith Baptist Church (B), 1979 February 8 (Box 468)
  - Fire Marshal/Michael Sinsigalli (B), 1979 February (Box 468)
  - [Fire Prevention/Firefighters], 1978-1979 (Box 468)
  - [Fire Protection - North Eastern Forest Fire Protection Comm.], 1978 (Box 468)
  - [Fire - U.S. Fire Administration], 1980 (Box 468)
  - Foster Grandparent Program (O), 1978 (Box 468)
  - Foster Grandparent Program/Thames Valley Council 10th Anniversary (O), 1978 (Box 468)
  - [Freedom of Information] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 468)
  - [General services Administration - US], 1979-1980 (Box 468)
  - [Get Well] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 468)
  - [Girl Scouts/Goodspeed Opera House] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 468)
  - [Government - Citizens Commission for Effective Government], 1980 (Box 469)
  - [Government - Hay Association - Salary Survey], 1979 (Box 469)
  - Governmental Expenditures, 1978 (Box 469)
  - Governor’s Committee on Fitness (B), 1978-1979 (Box 469)
  - [Governor’s Office - Activity Record], 1979 (Box 469)
  - [Governor’s Office - Activity Record], 1978 (Box 469)
  - [Governor’s Office - Staff/Misc.] (B), 1978 (Box 469)
  - [Governor’s Study Commission - Limitations of Gov’t. expenditure], 1978 (Box 469)
  - [Gun Control] (B), 1978 (Box 469)
  - Guyana, Jonestown (B), 1978-1979 (Box 469)
  - Health (Box 470)
    - [Arthritis], 1980 (Box 470)
    - Canton Wells Contamination, 1978 (Box 470)
    - [Commission on and Hearing Impaired], 1980 (Box 470)
    - [Commission on Hospital &Health Care], 1978-1980; 2 folders (Box 470)
    - CH &HC/Panel Report on Yale - New Haven Hospital, 1978 (Box 470)
    - [Conn. Hospital Association Bulletins], 1979 (Box 470)
    - [Dental Commission] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 470)
    - [Emergency Medical Service] (B), 1978 (Box 470)
    - Epilepsy (B), 1978 (Box 470)
    - [Handicapped] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 471)
    - [Health System Agency], 1978-1979 (Box 471)
    - [Hospitals] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 471)
    - [Immunization] (B), 1978 (Box 471)
    - Incentive Plan (B), 1978 (Box 471)
    - Job Action by Health Care Workers (B), 1979 June (Box 471)
    - Kellogg Foundation Grant (B), 1978 (Box 471)
    - [Letters] (Box 471)
      - A,B (B), 1978-1979 (Box 471)
      - C,D,E (B), 1978-1979 (Box 471)
      - F,G (B), 1978-1979 (Box 472)
      - H-L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 472)
      - M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 472)
      - N-R (B), 1978-1979 (Box 472)
      - S (B), 1978-1979 (Box 472)
      - R,U,V (B), 1978-1979 (Box 472)
      - W,X,Y,Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 473)
    - Mental Health (B), 1978-1979 (Box 473)
    - Mental Health/Deaf &Hearing Impaired (B), 1979 May (Box 474)
    - [Mental Health Misc.] (B), 1978 (Box 474)
    - Mental Retardation/FREDD Program (B), 1978 (Box 474)
    - [Mental Retardation - Letters A-G] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 474)
    - [Mental Retardation - Letters A-Z] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 474)
    - [Mental Retardation Misc.], 1978 (Box 474)
    - [Mental Retardation - Seaside Regional Center] (B), 1976 (Box 474)
    - Mental Retardation - Stonegate School (B), 1978 (Box 474)
    - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1977-1978 (Box 474)
    - [Nurses/Nursing Homes] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 474)
    - [Robert Wood Johnson Foundation] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 474)
    - Shellfish, 1977 (Box 474)
    - Southington Water (B), 1979 (Box 474)
    - [Southwest Conn. Health Systems Agency], 1980 (Box 474)
    - [Statewide Coordinating Council], 1978-1979 (Box 475)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital Expansion (B), 1979 March (Box 475)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital Misc., 1978-1979 (Box 475)
  - Health, Education &Welfare (HEW) (B), 1978 (Box 475)
  - [Health, Education &Welfare - U.S. Dept.], 1977 (Box 475)
  - [Health &Human services - U.S. Dept. of], 1978-1979 (Box 475)
  - [Historical] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 476)
  - [Hospice] (B), 1978 (Box 476)
  - Housing (Box 476)
    - [Central Housing Committee], 1978-1979 (Box 476)
    - Conference (B), 1978 April 11 (Box 476)
    - [Conn. Housing Finance Authority - CHFA], 1978-1979 (Box 476)
    - Court/Job as Housing Specialist, 1979 March 16 (Box 476)
    - [HUD] (B), 1978 (Box 476)
    - [Letters] (Box 476)
      - A-L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 476)
      - H-L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 476)
      - M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 477)
      - N-Z, 1978-1979 (Box 477)
  - [Housing - State Housing Advocate - M.M. Sharp] (B), 1978 (Box 477)
  - [Human Services - AFDC], 1978-1979 (Box 477)
  - [Human Services - Misc.], 1978-1979 (Box 477)
  - [Human Services Reorganization Commission], 1975-1977 (Box 478)
  - [Human Services Reorganization Commission], [1978]; 3 folders (Box 478)
  - [Human Services Reorganization Commission], [1979] (Box 479)
  - [Income Maintenance - Title XIX (B), 1979 (Box 479)
  - [Info Line], 1978 (Box 479)
  - [Information Bureau - Governor’s], 1978-1979 (Box 479)
  - [Insurance - Aetna], 1980 (Box 479)
  - [Insurance - Letters] (Box 479)
    - A,B,C (B), 1978-1979 (Box 479)
    - D,E,F,G,H (B), 1978-1979 (Box 479)
    - I,J,K,L,M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 479)
    - N,O,P,Q,R (B), 1978-1979 (Box 479)
    - S,T,U,V,W,X,Y,Z (Box 479)
  - [Insurance - Letters] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 480)
  - [Intergovernmental Programs/Relations] (O), 1978 (Box 480)
  - [Interior Dept. - Conn. Funding], 1978 (Box 480)
  - [Interior - U.S. Dept. of], 1978-1979 (Box 480)
  - [Internal Revenue Service] (Box 480)
  - Internal Catamaran Challenge/Trophy Match Races for “The Little America (Box 480)
  - Cup”, 1978 (Box 480)
  - [International Trade Commission], 1978 (Box 480)
  - [International Year of the Child] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 480)
  - [Interstate Commerce Commission], 1979 (Box 480)
  - [Interstate Commerce Commission], 1979-1980 (Box 481)
  - [Interstate Commerce Commission - Transportation Maps of the States], 1977 (Box 481)
  - Israel Visit (O), 1978 (Box 481)
  - [Judicial] (Box 481)
    - A-F (B), 1978-1979 (Box 481)
    - G-P (B), 1978-1979 (Box 481)
    - R-Z (B), 1978-1979 (Box 481)
  - [Judicial - Conn. Justice Commission] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 481)
  - Judicial/Judge Walter M. Picket (B), 1978 (Box 482)
  - [Judicial-Misc.] (B), 1978 (Box 482)
  - [Justice/Criminal - Search Group], 1979 (Box 482)